Ted, Ted, Ted!
Ted's got the ball!
Time's running out!
If he scores
this one,
then the Sharks
will go straight
to the
championship today.
Ted Vincent,
top star of the entire
college league.
If he keeps
strong tonight,
he is headed straight
for the NFL.
Ladies and gentlemen.
Ted! Ted! Ted!
Thirty yards!
Twenty!
Just ten to go!
Fuck!
Oh, my fucking leg!
Just wait.
Okay?
It's gonna heal.
All right?
Look, I...
I swear,
I can still walk.
Okay?
Fuck!
I'm sorry, Ted.
We can't sign a player
with a broken leg.
I'm very sorry.
No, no, I...
I'm not done yet.
Hey!
Such a waste.
He could've
gone pro,
maybe even
all-star level.
No team is going
to want him now.
He's not gonna
recover from this.
I swear.
Please.
I was born
to be a champion!
I'm still
a champion!
Fuck!
Coach West's
phone is still off!
Man, what the hell
are we going to do
without a head coach?
We don't even know
what play
we're going to run.
Then we'll run my plays.
My boys,
I need you to
listen up for good.
Okay?
They don't fuck
respect us out there.
All right?
We're coming
right up here.
Right up here, boys.
We got this.
You got to believe
in yourselves, okay?
All right, boys,
bring it in.
We'll bring it in.
Bring it in!
One, two, three.
Let's go! Come on!
Yes!
42:15!
The Eagles destroy
the Knights
and take the win.
That's what
we talked about.
Let's go!
Yes! Yes!
We just got beat by
an assistant coach?
Yes! Yes!
His plays are brilliant.
I need him
on my team.
Boss?
Nice work
out there today.
I've decided to
give you a raise.
Thank you, sir.
Two... two grand.
Oh my God, I...
I can finally
pay my bills.
I gotta tell my wife.
Babe!
I've got great news.
Wait...
This is West's jacket
and his whistle?
What the hell
are you doing?